Collection of salesmen's dummies, 1868-1932. Z1033.D85 A1
Lilly Library
- Salesmen's Dummies, 1868-1932
  - WHITE, TRUMBULL. Our New Possessions. Chicago: American Book Publishing House, [ca. 1898]. Phillippines, Puerto Rico, Cuba. Hawaii. (Box 5, Item 187.)
  - WIGGIN, KATE DOUGLAS. [Works]. Boston and New York: Houghton Mifflin, [ca. 1917]. "Autograph Edition." (Box 5, Item 188.)
  - WILDE, OSCAR. [Works?]. Garden City: Doubleday, Page, n.d. "Patrons' Edition De Luxe." (Box 5, Item 189.)
  - WILSON, JOSEPH T. The Black Phalanx; A History of the Negro Soldiers of the United States in the Wars of 1775-1812, 1861-'65. Hartford: American Publishing Company, 1892. (Box 5, Item 190.)
  - The World's Story: A History of the World in Story Song and Art. Boston and New York: Houghton Mifflin, 1914. (Box 5, Item 191.)
  - Standard Library Sets. New York and San Francisco: Wheeler Publishing Company, n.d. "Edition De Luxe." (Box 1, Item 192.)
  - Standard Authors in Fine Editions. New York: Thomas Y. Crowell, 1904. (Box 5, Item 193.)
  - Standard Sets. Kelmscott Edition. New York: Kelmscott Society, n.d. (Box 2, Item 194.)
  - Standard Sets. Kelmscott Edition. New York: Kelmscott Society. n.d. With different binding sample and expanded list of titles. (Box 2, Item 195.)
  - STEPHENS, ALEXANDER H. A Constitutional View of the Late War Between the States... Philadelphia: National Publishing Company. Chicago: Zeilger, McCurdy & Co, 1868. (Box 1, Item 196.)
  - TIER, JACK. The Works of James Fenimore Cooper. New York and London: G. P. Putnam and Sons. [n.d.] (Box 1, Item 197.)